<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BetFootball</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="basketball_maker">Basketball Maker</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="my_bets">My Bets</string>
    <string name="news">News</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">How to play</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="brightness">Brightness</string>
    <string name="vibration">Vibration</string>
    <string name="sound_volume">Sound volume</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_text">The player is given the chance to generate his own basketball standings from the available teams by playing matches according to the specified settings. The player\'s task is to achieve the victory of one of the teams by playing games with all opponents</string>
    <string name="choose_first_team">Choose first team</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="attacking_against_a_zone_defence">Attacking against a zone defence</string>
    <string name="choose_second_team">Choose second team</string>
    <string name="formation_team">Formation team</string>
    <string name="bet">Bet</string>
    <string name="first_team">first team</string>
    <string name="_000">000</string>
    <string name="vs">vs</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="second_team">second team</string>
    <string name="_1_25">1.25</string>
    <string name="place_a_bet_on_one_of_the_match_outcomes">Place a bet on one of the match outcomes</string>
    <string name="match_result">Match result</string>
    <string name="you_bet_on">"You bet on: "</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="wins">" wins"</string>
    <string name="draw">Draw</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="restart">Restart</string>
    <string name="dialog_title">Dialog Title</string>
    <string name="dialog_message">Dialog Message</string>
    <string name="congratulations_you_win">Congratulations! You win!</string>
    <string name="sorry_you_didn_t_win_this_time">Sorry, you did not win this time.</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="title1">AZAR IS TRYING TO BE DISSURED TO END CAREER</string>
    <string name="desc1">Midfielder Eden Hazard has not yet decided on his future.\n\nHe wants to end his career, but his entourage dissuades him, writes Foot Mercato. They want him to keep playing.\n\nHazard had options with Nice, Marseille, Lille, MLS clubs and Saudi Arabia. He rejected all offers.\n\nHazard left Real Madrid in May.</string>
    <string name="title2">EX-FORWARD DYNAMO MADE POKER IN CYPRUS CHAMPIONSHIP MATCH\n</string>
    <string name="desc2">AEK Larnaca played a draw with Ethnikos in the match of the 6th round of the Cypriot Championship.\n\nFour goals in the match were scored by forward Fran Sol for AEK. He scored a hat-trick before the break.\n\nHowever, he didn\'t help his team win. These are Sol\'s first goals for the new club.\n\nThe Spaniard joined AEK in the summer as a free agent. He left Dynamo.\n\nHe spent the last season on loan at Malaga, but scored only three goals there.</string>
    <string name="title3">TRUBIN\'S COMPETITOR IN BENFICA RECEIVED AN OFFER FROM THE Premier League</string>
    <string name="desc3">Benfica goalkeeper Odysseas Vlachodimos has come to the attention of Nottingham Forest, who are looking for a goalkeeper, according to insider Fabrizio Romano on Twitter.\n\nKeylor Navas defended the goal last season, who returned to PSG at the end of his loan.\n\nVlachodimos lost his place in based in Benfica after a quarrel with head coach Roger Schmidt.\n\nNottingham Forest estimates Vlachodimos at 9 million euros.\n\nIt was reported that Vlachodimos agreed on the terms of the contract with Manchester United.</string>
    <string name="title4">LEEDS ALMOST CLOSED RANGERS KAMARA DEAL</string>
    <string name="desc4">According to Fabrizio Romano, Leeds have officially offered terms to Rangers midfielder Glen Kamar.\n\nNegotiations between the clubs are in their final stages and the deal is expected to be finalized next week.\n\nThe 27-year-old Finnish player himself has already agreed to a move. \n\nGlen Kamara has been with the Rangers since January 2019. During this time, he accumulated 9 goals and 11 assists in 193 appearances for the club.</string>
    <string name="title5">VERRATTI MAY BE IN GALATASARAI\n</string>
    <string name="desc5">Marco Verratti received an offer from Turkey\'s Galatasaray\n\nIn addition, clubs from Saudi Arabia and Qatar continue to show serious interest in the 30-year-old Italian.\n\nTransfermarkt estimates the player at 40 million euros.</string>
    <string name="title6">BENFICA TRUBINA WAS BEAT IN THE PORTUGAL CHAMPIONSHIP WITH JIL VICENTE</string>
    <string name="desc6">"As part of the third round of the Portuguese championship, Benfica played away with Gil Vicente.\n\nDespite the high expectations from Ukrainian fans, goalkeeper Anatoly Trubin remained in Benfica's reserve. Local keeper Samuel Soares played at the base of the Eagles.\n\nBenfica took the lead in In the second half, Lisbon responded to two goals from the hosts with their two effective attacks. As a result, Roger Schmidt's team won 2:3. "</string>
    <string name="title7">FRESNEDA GOES TO SPORTING</string>
    <string name="desc7">Ivan Fresneda joins Sporting CP from Real Valladolid. This is reported by insider Fabrizio Romano.\n\nThe transfer amount will be 9 million euros + 3 million bonuses. The player will sign a contract until the summer of 2028.\n\nTransfermarkt estimates the full-back at 15 million euros.\n\nIt was previously reported that Sporting had contacted Napoli over Zanoli.</string>
    <string name="title8">КАСИЛЬЯС О РУБИАЛИСЕ: «ЭТО ПОЗОР»</string>
    <string name="desc8">Two-time Euro winner and World champion Iker Casillas reacted not to the decision of the President of the Spanish Football Federation to remain in his position.\n\nI think this is a disgrace.\n\n\nRecall that during the awarding of the winners in the final of the Women\'s World Cup, Rubiales allowed himself kiss on the lips of a Spanish football player.</string>
    <string name="title9">MOUTINHO IS A PLAYER OF BRAGA</string>
    <string name="desc9">Joao Moutinho moved to Braga.\n\nThe Portuguese joined the new team as a free agent. The midfielder signed a contract until the summer of 2024.\n\nThe player\'s salary will be only 400 thousand euros per season.\n\nLast season, Moutinho played in 36 matches for Wolverhampton, in which he scored 2 assists.\n\nPreviously it was reported that Man City have offered more than €50m for the Wolverhampton midfielder.</string>
    <string name="title10">SERGIO RAMOS CAN STILL MOVE TO TURKEY</string>
    <string name="desc10">Sergio Ramos, 37, a free agent, is in demand in the Turkish Super League.\n\nThe Real Madrid and Spain legend is now considering Galatasaray, according to insider Nicolo Schira.\n\nThe current Turkish champion has advanced in negotiations with the Spanish centre-back, which was previously traded by another Istanbul grandee - Besiktas.\n\nIt was previously reported that Ramos could continue his career in Milan.</string>
    <string name="title11">MUDRIK WAS AWARDED WITH A PRESTIGIOUS TITLE</string>
    <string name="desc11">Ukrainian midfielder of London Chelsea Mykhailo Mudryk received the title of Honorary Citizen of the city of Krasnograd, Kharkiv region, of which he is a native.\n\nMudryk was brought up in the academies of Metallist and Shakhtar. In January, the Ukrainian winger moved from the Donetsk club to London\'s Chelsea.\n\nThe City Council of Krasnograd on August 25 decided to award Mudrik the title of Honorary Citizen of the city.\n\nEarlier it was reported that the 22-year-old winger was injured.</string>
    <string name="title12">DI MARIA ON HIS RETURN TO BENFICA: \'I CHOOSE WITH MY HEART\'\nThe player had offers from Saudi Arabia</string>
    <string name="desc12">Experienced Argentina winger Angel Di Maria has returned to Portugal\'s Benfica this summer. The Argentine admitted that he received generous offers from Saudi Arabia, but rejected them:\n\n "I got a lot of calls from Saudi Arabia, they were crazy offers, but I chose with my heart, so I moved to Benfica," said the player.\n\ n\n Di Maria joined Benfica as a free agent after his contract with Juventus Turin expired.\n\nThe 35-year-old Argentine had previously played for the Eagles in 2007-2010.</string>
    <string name="title13">FURTHER VORSKLA? GREENWOOD AFTER EXPIRED FROM MANCHESTER UNITED IS GOING TO EXOTIC CHAMPIONSHIP\nThe Mancunians got rid of the pupil</string>
    <string name="desc13">Manchester United winger Mason Greenwood is in talks with an unnamed Albanian club, according to the Mirror.\n\nMan Utd announced on Monday that Greenwood would be leaving the club following an internal investigation.\n\nWhile other English clubs were speculated to be monitoring the striker\'s situation, the move the border would help reduce attention to himself on the field and beyond.\n\nIf Greenwood\'s move to Albania takes place, according to the good old tradition, the Englishman can go from the local championship to Vorskla, which has become the second home for a number of foreign players from the Balkans.\n\ Previously, clubs in Saudi Arabia refused to transfer Greenwood.</string>
    <string name="title15">DESCHAMPS: HENRI IS VERY HAPPY TO BE CHOSEN TO COACH THE YOUTH TEAM. He has taken over the U-21 team</string>
    <string name="desc15">France head coach Didier Deschamps spoke to L\'Equipe about Thierry Henry\'s appointment to the Under-21 team.\n\n"Thierry Henry is very pleased to have been chosen for this position. He was very motivated, I'm happy for him. He is one of those with whom I have always had a good relationship, built on great respect. If he had the opportunity to lead this team, then why not? It's like when you ask if a footballer made the right choice by joining a particular club. Unfortunately, we won't know about it right away.\nThierry will be judged by his results. By qualification for the next Euro, for the Olympic Games. Thierry is Thierry. He has credibility based on his playing career. He has experience as a coach, he is fully prepared, he will do his best.”\n\n\nHe will prepare the team for the 2024 Olympics.</string>
    <string name="teams">Teams</string>
    <string name="tactics">Tactics</string>
    <string name="player_name">Player Name</string>
    <string name="poland">Poland</string>
    <string name="positional_attack">Positional attack</string>
    <string name="counter_attack_fast_break">Counter-attack (fast break)</string>
    <string name="pressing_defence">Pressing defence</string>
    <string name="mixed_defence">Mixed defence</string>
    <string name="zone_defence">Zone defence</string>
    <string name="defence_against_the_ball_carrier">Defence against the ball carrier</string>
    <string name="tatcics_desc1">If an opponent puts up a zone defence, it is necessary to understand why they are doing it, why they find the weaknesses of this defence and how they can exploit them.\nThe basic principles of engagement against zone defences used by teams are as follows.\nTry to break up the zone with a quick attack before it is built;\nPreferably only run the ball for passing under the ring in search of an attack;\nAny receipt of the ball should show a threat, so the ball should be received in a comfortable attacking position;\nIf attempting to \"break up\" a zone from the inside, it should first be stretched with perimeter passes, making sure to threaten the ring with a shot, and then attempt to bring the ball to the penalty line or make a pass under the ring with the lead;\nWhen trying to break up a zone with free throws, it is important to move the ball around the perimeter as quickly as possible and for players to move so as to occupy areas of the court where there are no defenders;\nMost combinations used against a personal defence can also be used against a zone defence;\nPlayers must be able to recognise when and what kind of zone defence an opponent is using;\nOne effective \"breakdown\" of a zone defence is to overload (numerical advantage) the players on one side of the court;\nOnly take shots at the ring from prepared situations, when some players are ready to go for the rebound and others are ready to cover the rear\n</string>
    <string name="tatcics_desc2">Require your players to declare the combination that they are about to play on offense. Preferably they should do this in their own half of the pitch so that they don\'t waste time going from the back to the front. The combinations that will be used in this part of the match and that will be more effective are discussed with the players beforehand, so that everyone knows what the possible combinations are. The combinations are chosen by taking into account the weaknesses of the opponent\'s defence, the height or speed advantage of certain players over others, the possibility of the opponent changing defences, etc.\nThe objective is to find a free player to attack from a comfortable position or to create a one-on-one situation. A combination usually involves all five players. Usually one player creates a momentum for an attack while the other ones are able to act as a distraction, ready to create another attacking option or play some other role if necessary: covering the defense, fighting for rebounds, etc.\nThe formation of players should not in any way limit players and deprive them of creative initiative and the ability to \"create the game\" themselves. The combination is the backbone around which the attack is built. They are needed so that players know their roles and those of their partners clearly. Also, during any improvisation, players need to have an idea of what can come out of a particular move. Any improvisation should lead to a successful and comfortable attack, and the players must feel and understand each other so that the attack does not end with a loss or an awkward throw to the ring. Therefore, it is important to have combinations in the system that have multiple exits from certain situations.\n</string>
    <string name="tatcics_desc3">The fast break is the most spectacular and fastest way to score. Playing fast requires high technique. A high tempo will only be maintained if you keep the speed up to the technical improvement of your players, otherwise there will be more negatives (loose balls, runs, ill-conceived attacks) than positives. Therefore if you want to play fast and successfully you have to train and use all technical elements at high speed without defense, with passive resistance and with active resistance of defenders both in one-on-one, two-on-one, three-on-two situations and in numerical equal or minority situations.\nThe purpose of the counterattack is not only to try to move quickly to the opponent\'s ring, but also to be able to move the ball quickly by passing if there are free players, or by running the ball with different techniques to actively move forward. The task of the players is to create a triangle with the top on the line just above the penalty line, slightly to the right or left. This formation makes it easier to play a numerical advantage, it is easier to find an easy shot from long range or from under the ring.\n\n</string>
    <string name="tatcics_desc4">Pressing is the most active kind of defence, which puts firm pressure on the ball. It can be personal (all over the court; from your half) or zone (zone with traps; pressing, turning into zone defence, pressing 1/3/1, 2/2/1 2/1/2, etc.) and starts mainly when the opponent throws the ball in.\nThe main purpose of pressing is not only to put psychological pressure on the opponent, but also to try to break the opponent\'s successful play. It is a way of forcing opponents to make mistakes, take losses and launch quick, unprepared attacks at the end of possession. It is also an attempt to score quick and easy points. Pressing should not be used if the players in the team have not sufficiently mastered the principles of personal defence. It requires a high physical condition, good reserve potential and chemistry from all the players and links in the team, and it also requires the use of all the players in the team to maintain a high tempo and constant effective pressure on the opponents. Pressing can also be used as a deterrent, and it is used for more concentrated defensive play, for a later transition to zone defence or to prepare the defence by active pressing.\nPressing is also used as a system for long stretches of play and as a necessary measure: when losing a score, when you need to make quick interceptions and score easy points, to accelerate the tempo of the game or when waiting for the opponents to press.\nBy pressing, players try to take the ball away from their opponents, forcing them to make inaccurate passes that are easily intercepted. Often defenders, when they let a player out of their area, stop chasing them and become observers, which is a gross mistake. It is necessary to chase not only the player with the ball, trying to put pressure on him, but also to press players without the ball, forcing them to rush, worry and make mistakes.\nIf, in zone or personal pressing, a defender is left without a player and does not provide any assistance, this is a gross error. If one of the five pressers \"rests\", the work of the whole team has been done in vain. Pressing is first and foremost an active defence of the whole team.\nIn modern basketball many coaches tend to believe that active personal pressure is less effective, more difficult, more exhausting and leads not only to personal fouls, but also to unsportsmanlike comments, which are punished by 2 free throws and a possession for the opposing team. That is why it is used mainly as a deterrent pressure. More useful, energy-intensive, comfortable and versatile is zone pressure. Strong, technical players with good dribbling are able to handle personal pressure by themselves but zone pressure is difficult to break with dribbling.\n</string>
    <string name="tatcics_desc5">Mixed defence is the combination of area and personnel defence elements to provide a more effective defence against one or two opponents, the team leaders, who are having a good game. There are several types of mixed defence.\nFour players stand in a \'square\' (2-2 or 1-2-1) area defence with one defender guarding the opposition team leader.\nThree players form a triangle (2-1 or 1-2) and two defenders are personally guarding the opposing team\'s two leaders.\nOne player carries out the zone formation and four players personally guard the opponents.\nTwo players form a zone defence and three players form an individual defence.\nThe last two types of mixed defence are used very infrequently and mostly sporadically to create a bit of confusion for one or two attacks, to confuse players for unprepared attacks.\n</string>
    <string name="tatcics_desc6">The basic principle in zone defence is that each player is responsible for a specific part of the area, all players are linked together and shift according to the positioning of the attackers, their movement and the movement of the ball.\nAdvantages of zone defence:\nEnables players to be positioned on the court according to their physical and technical conditions. Tall, bouncy, strong players are placed in the zone underneath the basket, fast, agile players are placed just above the penalty line.\nMore team defence, easy to learn, able to compensate for individual defensive gaps.\nEncourages counterattacks and frequent interceptions and allows for low-risk defense: in case one defender fails, the zone shifts, and all players back each other up.\nThe number of fouls in zone defence is usually lower than in personal defence.\nThis defence is less vulnerable against pick-and-rolls.\nPretty flexible defense (can be built around the three point perimeter with opposing sharpshooters or concentrated in the three court with tall, powerful centre for the opposing team).\nEnergy-intensive defense, allowing leaders to pick up fewer defensive fouls.\nA team with zone defense can easily build mixed defensive formations or transitions (switching from zone defense to personnel defense and vice versa).\nDisadvantages of zone defense:\nInferior to personal defence in the psychological responsibility of the players, their charge to work individually on defence.\nWhen defending against teams with sharpshooters, the zone is abandoned when their attacks are successful.\nAs a rule, the corners of the court in zone defence are less protected, except for zone 1-3-1, in which not only the corners of the court, but also the sides of 45 degrees are less protected.\nZone defence is mostly used sporadically and is not the main form of defence. Zone defence is more effective at the middle or end of the game when opponents are tired and may make inaccurate, hurried shots.\nThere are several types of zone defence. Each of them is used in specific situations against specific opponents: zone defense 2-3 is effective against strong opponent\'s centres, zone 3-2 is effective against snipers, etc.\n</string>
    <string name="tatcics_desc7">A good basketball stance is important when defending against the ball carrier: centre of gravity is evenly distributed on both feet, support is on the toes, the foot is \"loaded\" (ready for any attacker action), knees bent, feet shoulder width apart and arms are at dribble level for a rebound attempt.\nIf an opponent has possession of the ball, one arm of the defender should be pointed at the ball and constantly attack the opponent, preventing him from aiming or throwing (best if it slightly touches the attacker), while the other arm should be slightly to the side in order to prevent a quick pass in time. Many defenders, being between the ball carrier and the basket even in a proper stance, do not actively act with their hands and do not put pressure on the player, especially important if the player has the ball in his hands after dribbling, thereby allowing the opponent to take further action calmly.\nContact defence against the ball carrier is a very difficult job, which mostly falls on the shoulders of perimeter players, a modern one with its own advantages.\nThe defender\'s movements should be practised regularly:\nin every training session - with and without resistance;\nwith one or two balls;\nwith one or two balls; with running steps.\nThe defender\'s actions in different situations can be divided into 9 positions:\nDefending against a player going with a lead to the ring.\nDefending against a player who has finished the lead and is trying to pass or take a shot at the ring.\nDefence against an attacker in his own half of the rink, but who has not used the lead.\nActions of defenders in a numerical minority.\nDefensive actions in a numerical advantage.\nForms of defence for pick-and-rolls.\nDefensive actions with and without the ball.\nDouble defence (used under pressure in corners and near the half court, pick-and-rolls, throw-ins).\nDefence against the first pass.\n</string>
    <string name="austria">Austria</string>
    <string name="colombia">Colombia</string>
    <string name="brazil">Brazil</string>
    <string name="germany">Germany</string>
    <string name="italy">Italy</string>
    <string name="argentina">Argentina</string>
    <string name="france">France</string>
    <string name="spain">Spain</string>
    <string name="netherlands">Netherlands</string>
    <string name="england">England</string>
    <string name="uruguay">Uruguay</string>
    <string name="portugal">Portugal</string>
    <string name="belgium">Belgium</string>
    <string name="sweden">Sweden</string>
    <string name="chile">Chile</string>
    <string name="mexico">Mexico</string>
    <string name="denmark">Denmark</string>
    <string name="switzerland">Switzerland</string>
    <string name="peru">Peru</string>
    <string name="choose_another_team">Choose another team</string>
</resources>